https://www.salestestonline.com/sales-personality-tests-privacy-policy

Take the guesswork out of hiring sales people
Use our sales test and never be fooled again!
Join thousands of satisfied customers - 97% re-order rate.
Privacy Policy
This privacy policy sets out how SalesTestOnline.com uses and protects any information that you give us when you use this website.
SalesTestOnline.com is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.
SalesTestOnline.com may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from February 15 2016.
What we collect
We may collect the following information:
name and job title
contact information including email address
demographic information such as postal/zip code, preferences and interests
other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers
What we do with the information we gather
We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:
Internal record keeping.
We may use the information to improve our products and services.
We may periodically send promotional email about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.
From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail.
We may use the information to customise the website according to your interests.
Security
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
How we use cookies
A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.
We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.
Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.
You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.
Links to other websites
Our website may contain links to enable you to visit other websites of interest easily. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide while visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
Questions? Call Us Now. 416.691.3661
HomeWhat We DoThe BenefitsWhy Choose UsLearn MoreFAQsSample ReportsTesting ProcessCustomizationGetting StartedPricing/Sign UpTestimonialsArticles and ToolsOur CompanyContact Us
Connect With Us:
FacebookLinkedInYouTubeTwitterGoogle+
Try a Free Demo test today.
Have a current employee take our sales personality test, or better yet, try it yourself. Once the sales personality test is taken and you see the results you'll be able to judge for yourself how accurate SalesTestOnline.com really is. Complete the form below now and we'll send you a password.
Fill out the fields...
so that we can send you the demonstration instructions
so that we can send you the demonstration instructions
so that we can send you the demonstration instructions
so that we can send you the demonstration instructions
so that we can send you the demonstration instructions
so that we can send you the demonstration instructions
so that we can send you the demonstration instructions
so that we can send you the demonstration instructions
...and that's it.
Try it Free Now
Thank You For Trying SalesTestOnline.
Thank you for your demo request. An email with instructions has been sent to the address you provided. That email will contain the necessary login and password information for you to take the sales personality test yourself or to have it taken by the person you named as the sales test taker. Please note that we offer one free demo sales personality test per company, unless otherwise arranged. Please also note that this is a service for businesses and is not intended for individual use. If you have questions and would like to speak with us please contact us at 416-691-3661.
Close
